[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐播放]
SURMA: One of the common issues we
SURMA：我们常见的问题之一
see when looking at people's sites
在查看人们的站点时看到
is that they don't cache resources
是他们不缓存资源
as well as they could.
尽他们所能。
For example, they set resources are
例如，他们将资源设置为
unlikely to change to expire after a few minutes,
几分钟后不太可能过期
and sometimes irregularly changing files
有时会不定期地更改文件
are set to cache for several weeks.
设置要缓存几个星期。
And then you get into cache-busting and fighting
然后您进入缓存破坏和战斗
with the browser's cache.
浏览器的缓存。
What you probably want to do instead
您可能想做什么
is to categorize your resources in one of two ways--
是通过以下两种方式之一对您的资源进行分类：
things that need to be validated with a server and things
需要通过服务器验证的事物和事物
that don't and can come straight from the HTTP cache.
不能，并且可以直接来自HTTP缓存。
Something that does normally need to be revalidated
通常确实需要重新验证的内容
is HTML, since that's the primary resource and the source
是HTML，因为这是主要资源和来源
of truth for your app.
您的应用程序的真实性。
Here you want a cache note like this-- private, no-cache.
在这里，您需要这样的缓存说明-私有，非缓存。
That tells the browser that the resource is intended
告诉浏览器该资源是预期的
for just that user and that it should check with the server
仅针对该用户，并且应该与服务器核对
before serving it.
上菜之前
Things that don't need to be validated
不需要验证的事情
would be things like JavaScript, CSS, or images.
可能是JavaScript，CSS或图片之类的东西。
Here, you'll want to tell the browser that it should cache
在这里，您将要告诉浏览器它应该缓存
the resource for like a year.
一年的资源。
But what do you do if you need to change that resource?
但是，如果您需要更改该资源怎么办？
You include a hash or a [? version ?] name
您包括一个哈希或[？版本？]名称
in the resources path.
在资源路径中。
There are plenty of build tools that
有很多构建工具
can help you achieve just that.
可以帮助您实现这一目标。
Bear in mind that you shouldn't be caching your HTML, which
请记住，您不应该缓存HTML，
means that when you change the far future cache resource,
意味着当您更改远期缓存资源时，
you can update the reference to it in the HTML and everything
您可以在HTML和所有内容中更新对此的引用
should just work out.
应该就解决了。
If you want to see what your caching headers are,
如果您想查看缓存标题是什么，
head to Dev Tools, Network Panel, click on a resource,
转到“开发工具”，“网络面板”，单击资源，
and choose the Headers tab.
并选择标题标签。
Laters.
以后
For more on this topic, you can watch the Supercharged
有关此主题的更多信息，您可以观看机械增压
livestream I did on server-side rendering over there,
我在那边进行服务器端渲染的实时流，
or read Jake's blog post, which we link to in the description.
或阅读我们在说明中链接到的Jake的博客文章。
But more importantly-- you actually know.
但更重要的是-您实际上知道。